Guide to the Belva Kibler and Donald Morgan Collection
Stanford Archive of Recorded Sound
- Menotti, Gian Carlo, 1911-2007. MediumFeb. 15, 1959 (Othertype 22, Folder 22)
- Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Matthäuspassion I. Selections (Othertype 22, Folder 23)
  Kibler, Belva, 1913-1983, alto
- Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Matthäuspassion II. Selections (Othertype 22, Folder 24)
- Schoenberg, Arnold, 1874-1951. Buch der hängenden Gärten (Othertype 22, Folder 25)
  Kibler, Belva, 1913-1983
- First Church Choir Concert I. June 10, 1987 (Othertype 22, Folder 26)
  Yale University, Woolsey Hall
- First Church Choir Concert II. June 10, 1987 (Othertype 22, Folder 27)
- Franck, César, 1822-1890. Panis angelicusAug. 29, 1987 (Othertype 22, Folder 28)
  Morgan, Donald P., bass baritone
- Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Zauberflöte. SelectionsJune 19, 1988 (Othertype 22, Folder 29)
  Morgan, Donald P., bass baritone; Mitchell, Ruth, piano
- Morgan, Donald P. A music memorial IJuly 22, 1995 (Othertype 22, Folder 30)
- Morgan, Donald P. A music memorial IIJuly 22, 1995 (Othertype 22, Folder 31)
- Brahms, Johannes, 1833-1897. Vocal compositions. (Othertype 22, Folder 32)
  Copied from Victor 6015 and M-522
- Schoenberg, Arnold, 1874-1951. Buch der hängenden Gärten. IOct.8,1952, 10 1/2 " reel; 15" speed (Othertype 23, Folder 1)
- Schoenberg, Arnold, 1874-1951. Buch der hängenden Gärten. IOct.8,1952, 10 1/2 " reel; 15" speed (Othertype 23, Folder 2)
- Schoenberg, Arnold, 1874-1951.Buch der hängenden Gärten. IIOct.8,1952, 10 1/2 " reel; 15" speed (Othertype 23, Folder 3)
- Schoenberg, Arnold, 1874-1951. Buch der hängenden Gärten. IIOct.8,1952, 10 1/2 " reel; 15" speed (Othertype 23, Folder 4)
- Jürgen von Manger I, sound disc: 33 1/3 rpm, vinyl; 12 in. (Othertype 23, Folder 1)
  Sleeve annotation: "Berlin April 1971. Lieber Don in dankbarer Erinnerung an unsere gemaisame Reise und Arbeit. Herbert. Annotations on cardboard packing: Lieber Don, sicher hast Du mit dem "Original" genau so viel Spass, wie bei Carl's Improvisationen - ganz herzliche Grüsse, Carl und Herbert April 13, 1971
- Jürgen von Manger II, sound disc: 33 1/3 rpm, vinyl; 12 in. (Othertype 23, Folder 2)
  Annotations on cardboard packing: Lieber Don, sicher hast Du mit dem "Original" genau so viel Spass, wie bei Carl's Improvisationen - ganz herzliche Grüsse, Carl und Herbert April 13, 1971
- Evening Star, sound disc: 78 rpm, shellac; 12 in. (Othertype 23, Folder 3)
  Sung by Donald Morgan
- Evening Star, sound disc: 78 rpm, shellac; 12 in. (Othertype 23, Folder 4)
- Evening Star, sound disc: 78 rpm, shellac; 12 in. (Othertype 23, Folder 5)
- Evening Star, sound disc: 78 rpm, shellac; 12 in. (Othertype 23, Folder 6)
- Evening Star, sound disc: 78 rpm, shellac; 12 in. (Othertype 23, Folder 7)
- Evening Star, sound disc: 78 rpm, shellac; 12 in. (Othertype 23, Folder 8)
- Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Ernani. Infelice! e tu credevi Aug. 2, 1949, sound disc: 78 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Othertype 23, Folder 9)
  Eby, James Brian, 1896-, baritone; Lawson, Jean, piano
- Music from the Columbia Picture The Brave Bulls, sound disc: 33 1/3 rpm, vinyl; 12 in. (Othertype 23, Folder 10)
  Based on Virgen of Macerana (Southern Music); Cielo Andaluz (Peer International)
- Lieder I, Transcription disc: 78 rpm, laquer on cardboard; 9 3/4 in. Preservation needed (Othertype 23, Folder 11)
  "This was first recorded, and not so good, but speaking parts is all right." Disc encasing possibly for the three Lieder discs with the annotation, "Aufnahmen von der Abschiedsfeier für Herrn Dr. Morgan im Gästehaus der Anorgana - US Administration-Burgkirchen/Alz, Obb. am 10. Oct. 1949. Es singt Herr Dr. Morgan, am Flügel Herr Dr. Kienz."
- Lieder II, Transcription disc: 78 rpm, laquer on cardboard; 9 3/4 in. Preservation needed (Othertype 23, Folder 12)
  Grieg, Edvard, 1843-1907. Hjertets melodier. Jeg elsker dig -- Loewe, Carl, 1796-1869. Lieder, op. 145. Meeresleuchten
- Lieder III, Transcription disc: 78 rpm, laquer on cardboard; 9 3/4 in. Preservation needed (Othertype 23, Folder 13)
  Loewe, Carl, 1796-1869. Lieder, op. 145. Meeresleuchten. With annotation, "This is the best record."
- Copland, Aaron, 1900-1990. Symphonies, no. 3. Part IDec. 21, 1947, Sound disc: 78 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 23, Folder 14)
  New York Philharmonic. Included with the records: letter to Mrs. Charles Chaplin from Dr. John Vincent from University of California. Dec. 10, 1948 and autograph by Aaron Copland: "For Mrs. Chaplin with cordial greetings. Aaron Copland. Dec. 7, 1948 - UCLA"
- Copland, Aaron, 1900-1990. Symphonies, no. 3. Part IIDec. 21, 1947, Sound disc: 78 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 23, Folder 15)
- Copland, Aaron, 1900-1990. Symphonies, no. 3. Part IIIDec. 21, 1947, Sound disc: 78 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 23, Folder 16)
- Copland, Aaron, 1900-1990. Symphonies, no. 3. Part IVDec. 21, 1947, Sound disc: 78 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 23, Folder 17)
- Copland, Aaron, 1900-1990. Symphonies, no. 3. Part VDec. 21, 1947, sound disc: 78 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 23, Folder 18)
- Love is the sweetest thing, sound disc: 78 rpm, acetate with a galss base; 12 in. Disc broken (Oversize 4, Folder 19)
- Belangrijke Uitvoering. Te venlo. Haydn, Joseph, 1732-1809. Schöpfung April 26 (Othertype 24, Folder 1)
  Concergebow. Prin van Oranje. Morgan, Donald P, bass
- Staatliches Kurhaus. Bad Reichenhall. Sonder-KonzertSept. 4, 1936 (Othertype 24, Folder 2)
  Morgan, Donald P, bass-baritone; Rosen, Hans, piano; Sauer, Josef, concert master; Kräusslich, Emil, solo cello. Staatlicher Kurorchester. Werner, Florenz, conductor
- Goethe Festival Concert. The British Goethe Festival Society. LondonJune 22 (Othertype 24, Folder 3)
  Lampmann, Else, contralto; Morgan, Donald, bass. Settings of Goehte's poems.
- Bavaria, Hesse, Wurtemberg, Baden. US Zone (Othertype 24, Folder 4)
- Water color of Belva Kibler (Box 6, Folder 1)
  Artist unkown
- Miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 1)
  Hollywood Bowl pamphlet; Typed script "As husbands go"; Texts to J.S. Bach works; Floor plan for apartment complex; postcard with photo of Arturo Toscanini